Guide to the Group Research, Inc. Records,
Rare Book and Manuscript Library Columbia University Libraries
- Series I: Topical Files
  - Christian Crusade Newspaper clippings, Tulsa, OK, 1966-8 (Box 67)
  - Christian Crusade Newspaper clippings, Tulsa, OK, 1963-5 (Box 67)
  - Christian Crusade Newspaper clippings, Tulsa, OK, 1960-2 (Box 67)
  - Christian Crusade Magazine and "Congressional Record" clippings, Tulsa, OK (Box 67)
  - Christian Crusade "Operation Midnight Ride", Tulsa, OK (Box 67)
  - Christian Crusade Staff, Tulsa, OK (Box 67)
  - Christian Crusade Meetings, conventions, leadership schools, etc., Tulsa, OK (Box 67)
  - Christian Crusade Publications, Tulsa, OK (Box 67)
  - Christian Defense League (Box 67)
  - "Christian Economics ", New York, NY (Box 67)
    [Published by Christian Freedom Foundation See also Howard Kershner, Christian Freedom Foundation, and the Group Research directory under "Christian Economics."]
  - Christian Educational Association, Union, NJ (Box 68)
    [See also "Common Sense," Conde McGinley, and the Group Research directory under Christian Educational Association.]
  - Christian Freedom Foundation, Inc. New York, NY, 1971 (Box 68)
    [See also the Group Research directory under Christian Freedom Foundation, Inc.]
  - Christian Freedom Foundation, Inc. "Christian Economics", New York, NY (Box 68)
    [Editor, Howard Kershner See also Howard Kershner and "Christian Economics."]
  - Christian Herald (Box 68)
  - Christian Heritage Center (Box 68)
  - Christian Heritage Church (Box 68)
    [See also Griswold, Ferrell.]
  - Christian Law Institute (Box 68)
  - Christian Mandate for America (Box 68)
  - Christian Nationalist Crusade America First (Box 68)
  - Christian Nationalist Crusade Letters from headquarters (Box 69)
  - Christian Nationalist Crusade General, newspaper clippings, financial, 1972- (Box 69)
  - Christian Nationalist Crusade General, newspaper clippings, financial (Box 69)
  - Christian Nationalist Crusade Publications other than letters (Box 69)
  - Christian Nationalist Crusade "Cross and the Flag, The", Los Angeles, CA (Box 70)
    [Publisher, Gerlad L. K. Smith Former Editor, Chalres F. Robertson See also the Group Research directory under "Cross and the Flag, The."]
  - Christian Nationalist Crusade Publications other than letters, 1974- (Box 70)
  - Christian Patriots, Inc. "Think" (Box 70)
  - Christian Patriots of Michigan (Box 70)
  - Christian Rescue Effort for the Emancipation of Dissidents (CREED) (Box 70)
  - Christian Research "Facts for Action", Minneapolis, MN (Box 70)
    [See also the Group Research directory under Christian Research.]
  - Christian Resistance (Box 70)
  - Christian Scientists to Combat Communism in the Christian Science Movement (Box 70)
  - Christian Voice, 1987- (Box 70)
  - Christian Voice, 1982- (Box 70)
  - Christian Voice (Box 71)
  - Christian Women's Clubs of America (Box 71)
  - Christian Youth Against Communism (Box 71)
  - Christian Youth Corps (Box 71)
    [See also National Renaissance Party and "The Middle Path."]
  - Christian Youth for America (Box 71)
    [See also Soldiers of the Cross and Kenneth Goff.]
  - Christianform, The (Box 71)
    [See also Cuban Freedom Committee.]
  - Christianity Today (Box 71)
  - Christians for a Better America (Box 71)
  - Church and State -- Separation of (Box 71)
    [See also POAUSCS.]
  - Church League of America Financial Information, Wheaton, IL (founded in) (Box 72)
    [See also Edgar C. Bundy and the Group Research directory under Church League of America, under "A Manual for Survival" (a book compiled and published by the Church League of America), and under "News and Views" (newsletter of the Church League of America).]
  - Church League of America General information, Wheaton, IL (founded in), 1976- (Box 72)
  - Church League of America General information, Wheaton, IL (founded in) (Box 72)
  - Church League of America Letters from Headquarters, Wheaton, IL (founded in), 1976- (Box 72)
  - Church League of America Letters from Headquarters, Wheaton, IL (founded in) (Box 72)
  - Church League of America Publications (except "News and Views"), Wheaton, IL (founded in) (Box 73)
  - Church of Christian Liberty (Box 73)
  - Church of God (Box 73)
  - Churches -- Air Force Manual and Related Controversy (Box 73)
  - Churches (Box 73)
  - Churches Against Communism (Box 73)
  - Churches of Christ (Box 73)
  - Churchman, The (Box 73)
  - Cincinnati Open Forum (Box 73)
  - "Cincinnatus" (an alias) (Box 73)
  - Cinema Educational Guild, Inc. Publications, Hollywood, CA (Box 74)
    [See also the Group Research directory under Cinema Educational Guild, Inc.]
  - Cinema Educational Guild, Inc. Hollywood, CA (Box 74)
  - Circuit Riders, Inc. Cincinnati, OH (incorporated in) (Box 74)
    [See also the Group Research directory under Circuit Riders, Inc.]
  - "Citizen, The", Frostburg, MD (Box 74)
    [See the Group Research directory under "Citizen, The" from Jackson, MS rather than Frostburg, MD.]
  - Citizen Speaks, The (Box 74)
  - Citizens Action Committee (Box 74)
  - Citizens Against Communism (Box 74)
  - Citizens Anti-Communism Committee of Connecticut (Box 75)
  - Citizens Commission Against Crime (Box 75)
  - Citizens Commission on the Crisis in the Americas (Box 75)
  - Citizens Commission for a Free Cuba (Box 75)
  - Citizens Committee for Balanced Legislative Representation (Box 75)
  - Citizens Committee for Better Government (Box 75)
  - Citizens Committee for Conservatives (Box 75)
  - Citizens Committee for Constitutional Liberties (Box 75)
  - Citizens Committee for Extension of the National Defense Education Act (Box 75)
  - Citizens Committee for Hoover Report (Box 75)
  - Citizens Committee for the Outdoor Recreation Resources Review Commission Report (Box 75)
  - Citizens Committee for Peace with Freedom in Vietnam (Box 75)
  - Citizens Committee for Peace with Security (Box 75)
  - Citizens Committee on American Policy in the Near East (Box 75)
  - Citizens Committee to Preserve Taft-Hartley, Inc. (Box 75)
  - Citizens Committee to Safeguard America, The (Box 75)
  - Citizens Committee on State Legislatures (Box 75)
  - Citizens Congressional Committee, Los Angeles, CA and Washington, DC (Box 75)
    [See also Opal Tanner White and the Group Research directory under Citizens Congressional Committee.]
  - Citizens' Councils Newspaper clippings, 1969-70 (Box 76)
  - Citizens' Councils Newspaper clippings, 1968- (Box 76)
  - Citizens' Councils Newspaper clippings, 1965-7 (Box 76)
  - Citizens' Councils Newspaper clippings, 1963-4 (Box 76)
  - Citizens' Councils Newspaper clippings, 1954-62 (Box 76)
  - Citizens' Councils Financial and Postal (Box 76)
  - Citizens' Councils Notes and miscellany (Box 76)
  - Citizens' Councils Reports and studies on (Box 76)
  - Citizens' Councils Their material (Box 76)
  - Citizens' Defense Fund (Box 76)
  - Citizens for a New Prosperity (Box 76)
  - Citizens for a Sound Economy (Box 76)
  - Citizens for America (Box 77)
  - Citizens for American Survival (Box 77)
  - Citizens for Constitutional Government (Box 77)
    [See also Missouri in Series 3 -- States.]
  - Citizens for Constructive Action (Box 77)
  - Citizens for Constructive Education (Box 77)
  - Citizens for Control of Federal Spending (Box 77)
  - Citizens for Educational Freedom (Box 77)
  - Citizens for Freedom (Box 77)
  - Citizens for Goldwater (Box 77)
    [See also Citizens Committee for Conservatives.]
  - Citizens for Good Government (Box 77)
  - Citizens for Judicial Restraint, Inc. (Box 77)
  - Citizens for Justice with Order (Box 77)
  - Citizens for National Defense (Box 77)
  - Citizens for Public Prayer (Box 77)
  - Citizens for the Preservation of Constitutional Government (Box 78)
  - Citizens for the Preservation of States Rights and Constitutional Government (Box 78)
  - Citizens for the Republic (Box 78)
  - Citizens Foreign Aid Committee General, Washington, DC (Box 78)
    [See also the Group Research directory under Citizens Foreign Aid Committee and under Special Reports -- Citizens Foreign Aid Committee.]
  - Citizens Foreign Aid Committee Studies and testimony of, Washington, DC (Box 78)
  - Citizens Foreign Relations Committee, New York, NY (Box 79)
    [Former Chairman, F. G. Reinicke See also the Group Research directory under Citizens Foreign Relations Committee.]
  - Citizens Information Center (Box 79)
  - Citizens Intelligence Digest (Box 79)
  - Citizens' Legal Defense Fund for the FBI (Box 79)
  - Citizen's Legislative Information Program (Box 79)
  - Citizens National Committee, Inc. (Box 79)
  - Citizens National Committee for Higher Education, Inc. (Box 79)
  - Citizens Research Council of Michigan (Box 79)
  - Citizens' Research Foundation (Box 79)
  - Citizens United-Press (Box 79)
  - Citrus Americanism Center (Box 79)
  - Civic Affairs Associates, Inc. Voting records, Washington, DC (Box 79)
    [See also the Group Research directory under Civic Affairs Associates, Inc. and under Special Reports -- Voting Records and Indexes.]
  - Civic Association of America (Box 79)
  - Civic Films, Inc. (Box 79)
  - Civil Defense (Box 79)
  - Civil Rights -- General (Box 79)
  - Civil Rights -- Splinter Groups (Box 80)
  - Civil Rights Bill (Box 80)
  - "Civil Riots USA: The Watts Story" [film] (Box 80)
    [See also Constructive Action, Inc.]
  - Civitan International (Box 80)
  - Claremont Men's College, Claremont, CA (Box 80)
  - Clark, Fred George (Box 80)
    [Founder, American Economic Foundation See also the Group Research directory under Fred George Clark.]
  - Clark, J. Philip (Box 80)
  - Clark, J. Reuben (Box 80)
  - Clark, James G. (Sheriff) (Box 80)
  - Clark, Mark (Gen.) (Box 80)
  - Clausen, Don H. (Box 80)
  - Clay, James H. B. (Box 80)
  - Clay, Lucius D. (Gen.) (Box 80)
  - Clergy Economic Education Foundation (Box 80)
  - Clergymen's Committee on China (Box 80)
  - Clergymen's Emergency Committee on China (Box 80)
  - Cline, Ray S. (Box 80)
  - Clinton, William "Bill" (Box 80)
  - Clinton, William "Bill" Cabinet (Box 80)
  - Clinton, William "Bill" Staff (Box 80)
  - Coal Industry Committee on Mine Safety (Box 80)
  - Coalition for Asian Peace and Security (Box 81)
  - Coalition for Freedom (Box 81)
  - Coalition for Religious Freedom (Box 81)
  - Coalition on National Priorities and Military Policy (Box 81)
  - Coast Federal Savings and Loan Clippings (Box 81)
  - Coast Federal Savings and Loan Materials distributed (Box 81)
    [1 of 2 folders]
  - Coast Federal Savings and Loan Materials distributed (Box 81)
    [2 of 2 folders]
  - Coast Federal Savings and Loan Reports on and miscellaneous (Box 81)
  - Coca-Cola Company (Box 81)
  - Coe Foundation, The (Box 81)
  - Cohn, Roy M. (Box 81)
  - Colbert, James D. (Box 82)
  - Cold War Council (Box 82)
  - Cold War Seminar (Box 82)
  - Coldren, Fred (Box 82)
  - Colegrove, Kenneth (Dr.), New York, NY (Box 82)
    [Professor of Political Science, C. W. Post College, Long Island University See also the Group Research directory under Dr. Kenneth Colegrove.]
  - Coleman Foundation (Box 82)
  - Colonial Dames of America (Box 82)
  - Colonial Daughters of the Seventeenth Century (Box 82)
  - Colson, Charles W. (Box 82)
  - Colt Foundation (Box 82)
  - Columbia Publishing Company (Box 82)
  - Columbians, The (Box 82)
  - "Combat, Inc." (Box 82)
    [Publication of the National Review.]
  - Combine, The, California (Box 82)
  - Committee Against Summit Entanglements, Belmont, MA (Box 82)
    [See also the Group Research directory under Committee Against Summit Entanglements.]
  - Committee for a Free China (Box 82)
  - Committee for American Principles (Box 83)
  - Committee for Citizens for the Preservation of the Sovereignty of the United States of America (Box 83)
  - Committee for Conservative Action (Box 83)
  - Committee for Constitutional Government (Box 83)
  - Committee for Constitutional Government (Box 83)
  - Committee for Constitutional Integrity (Box 83)
  - Committee for Economic Development (Box 83)
  - Committee for Equal Anti-Trust Law Protection, South Bend, IN (Box 84)
    [Associated with Manion Forum. See also the Group Research directory under Committee for Equal Anti-Trust Law Protection.]
  - Committee for Freedom for All Peoples (Box 84)
  - Committee for Government of the People (Box 84)
  - Committee for Improved Education (Box 84)
  - Committee for Monetary Research & Education (Box 84)
  - Committee for Pillion Resolution (Box 84)
  - Committee for Public Justice (Box 84)
  - Committee for Responsible Youth Politics (Box 84)
  - Committee for the Free World (Box 84)
  - Committee for the Monroe Doctrine, New York, NY (Box 84)
    [1 of 2 folders. See also the Group Research directory under Committee for the Monroe Doctrine.]
  - Committee for the Monroe Doctrine, New York, NY (Box 84)
    [2 of 2 folders.]
  - Committee for the Nation (Box 84)
  - Committee for the Survival of a Free Congress (Box 85)
  - Committee for the Survival of a Free Congress, 1978 (Box 85)
  - Committee for the Survival of a Free Congress, 1982 (Box 85)
  - Committee for the Survival of a Free Congress, 1987 (Box 86)
  - Committee for the Survival of a Free Congress, 1994 (Box 86)
  - Committee for Truth in Politics (Box 86)
  - Committee for Voluntary Unionism (Box 86)
  - Committee for Welfare Reform (Box 86)
  - Committee of Black Americans for Truth about the Middle East (COMBATAME) (Box 86)
  - Committee of Catholic Laymen Pro Ecclesia (Box 86)
  - Committee of Christian Laymen (Box 86)
  - Committee of Correspondence (Box 86)
  - Committee of Endorsers (Box 86)
    [See also Citizens' Foreign Relations Committee.]
  - Committee of Hoover Commission Task Force Members (Box 86)
  - Committee of One Million (Against the Admission of Red China to the United Nations) General Information (Box 87)
  - Committee of One Million (Against the Admission of Red China to the United Nations) Letters from Headquarters (Box 87)
  - Committee of One Million (Against the Admission of Red China to the United Nations), 1971 (Box 87)
  - Committee of One Million (Against the Admission of Red China to the United Nations) Pamphlets (Box 87)
  - Committee of One Million Caucasians to March on Congress (Box 88)
  - Committee of Responsible Americans to Support the President and Our Armed Forces (Box 88)
  - Committee of Southern Churchmen (Box 88)
  - Committee of Ten Million (Box 88)
  - Committee of Ten Million, 1981 (Box 88)
  - Committee of the States (Box 88)
  - Committee on American Leadership (Box 88)
  - Committee on Americanism of National Sojourners, Inc. (Box 88)
  - Committee on Pan-American Policy, New York, NY and incorporated in Washington, DC (Box 88)
    [See also Allen A. Zoll and Harold Lord Varney as well as the Group Research directory under Committee on Pan-American Policy.]
  - Committee on State Sovereignty, Inc. Washington, DC (Box 88)
    [See also David Molthrop.]
  - Committee on the Present Danger (Box 88)
  - Committee on the Triple Revolution (Box 88)
  - Committee to Celebrate the Liberation of France (Box 88)
  - Committee to Defeat the Union Bosses' Candidates (Box 88)
  - Committee to End Aid to the Soviet Union (Box 88)
  - Committee to Protect the Family (Box 88)
  - Committee to Unite America, Inc. (Box 88)
  - Committee to Warn of the Arrival of Communist Merchandise on the Local Business Scene (Box 88)
  - Common Cause (Box 89)
  - "Common Sense", Union, NJ (Box 89)
    [Editor, Conde McKinley Publisher, Christian Educational Association See also Conde McKinley, Christian Educational Association, and the Group Research directory under "Common Sense."]
  - Communications, Inc. (Box 89)
  - Communications Distribution Inc. (Box 89)
  - Communications Network of America (Box 89)
  - Communications Political Action Committee (Box 89)
  - Communism on the Map (Box 89)
  - Communist Party, U.S.A. (Box 89)
  - Communist-Made Goods (Box 89)
  - Communist Rules for Revolution (Box 89)
  - Communist Target - Youth (Box 89)
  - Community Action U.S.A. (Box 89)
  - Community Lecture Series (Box 89)
  - Community Relations Council of Los Angeles (Box 89)
  - Concerned Catholic Parents (Box 89)
  - Concerned Christians (Box 89)
  - Concerned Citizens (Box 89)
  - Concerned Presbyterians (Box 89)
  - Concerned Women for America (Box 90)
  - Confederate Air Force (Box 90)
  - Conference Board, The (Box 90)
  - Conference of American Small Business Organizations (Box 90)
  - Conference of National Organizations (Box 90)
  - Conference on Preserving the Democratic Process (Box 90)
  - CONGO Material concerning the kidnapping of Molse Tshombe (Box 90)
  - Congress for Cultural Freedom (Box 90)
    [See also Association for Cultural Freedom.]
  - Congress of Conservatives (Box 90)
  - Congress of Freedom, Inc. Omaha, NE (Box 90)
    [See also the Group Research directory under Congress of Freedom, Inc. and under "The Greater Nebraskan" (official publication of the Congress of Freedom, Inc.).]
  - Congress of Racial Equality (Box 90)
  - Congressional Action Fund (Box 91)
  - Congressional Award, The (Box 91)
  - Congressional Club, The (Box 91)
    [A PAC association with Sen. Jesse Helms (R- NC).]
  - Congressional Ethics (Box 91)
  - Congressional Majority Committee (Box 91)
  - Conlan, John B. (Box 91)
  - Connally, John B. (Box 91)
  - Conservatism USA (CUSA) (Box 91)
  - "Conservative, The" (Box 91)
  - Conservative Action Foundation (Box 91)
  - Conservative Awards Dinner (Box 91)
  - Conservative Book Club (Box 91)
    [See also Series 2 -- Conservative Book Club.]
  - Conservative Books by Mail, Inc. (Box 91)
  - Conservative Caucus, 1990- (Box 91)
  - Conservative Caucus, Inc. (Box 91)
  - Conservative Caucus, 1986- (Box 92)
  - Conservative Caucus, 1984- (Box 92)
  - Conservative Caucus, 1982- (Box 92)
  - Conservative Caucus, 1979- (Box 93)
  - Conservative Digest, The, MO (Box 93)
  - Conservative Digest (Box 93)
  - Conservative Federation of Michigan, The (Box 93)
  - Conservative Leadership Conference (Box 93)
  - Conservative Legal Defense and Education Fund (Box 93)
  - Conservative Opportunity Society (Box 93)
  - Conservative National Committee (Box 93)
  - Conservative Network (Box 93)
  - Conservative Opportunity Society (Box 93)
  - Conservative Party (Box 93)
  - Conservative Party General (Box 94)
  - Conservative Party of New York, 1972- (Box 94)
  - Conservative Party of New York (Box 94)
  - Conservative Party of Iowa (Box 94)
    [See also the Group Research directory under Conservative Party of Iowa.]
  - Conservative Party, AL, CA, FL, KS, MO, NM, and WI (Box 94)
  - Conservative Party of Pennsylvania (Box 94)
  - Conservative Party of Texas (Box 94)
  - Conservative Party of Virginia (Box 94)
  - Conservative Tide, The (Box 94)
  - Conservative Victory Committee, The (Box 94)
  - Conservative View, The (Box 94)
  - Conservatives Against Liberal Legislation (Box 94)
  - Conspiracy -- theories and related materials (Box 95)
  - Constitution and Free Enterprise Foundation (Box 95)
  - Constitution-News-Review (Box 95)
  - Constitution Party (Box 95)
  - Constitution Parties Includes material on CA, CO, FL, MD, MN, NM, and PA. (Box 95)
  - Constitutional Alliance, Lansing, MI and Washington, DC (Box 95)
    [See also the Group Research directory under Constitutional Alliance and under "Success" (the monthly publication of Constitutional Alliance).]
  - Constitutional Educational League (Box 95)
  - Constitutional Guardian (Box 95)
  - Constitutional Prayer Foundation (Box 95)
  - Constitutional Provisional Government of the United States (Box 95)
    [Founded by Brig. Gen. Herbert C. Holdridge.]
  - Constructive Action, Inc. Whittier, CA (Box 96)
    [See also the Group Research directory under Constructive Action, Inc.]
  - Consumer Alert (Box 96)
  - Consumers Union (Box 96)
  - Cooley, Oscar W. (Box 96)
  - Coordinating Committee for Fundamental American Freedoms "Congressional Record" clippings, Washington, DC (Box 96)
    [See also the Group Research directory under Coordinating Committee for Fundamental American Freedoms.]
  - Coordinating Committee for Fundamental American Freedoms Financial records, Washington, DC (Box 96)
  - Coordinating Committee for Fundamental American Freedoms General, Washington, DC (Box 96)
  - Coordinating Committee for Fundamental American Freedoms Newspaper clippings, Washington, DC (Box 96)
    [See also Civil Rights and Alabama Sovereignty Commission.]
  - Coordinating Committee for Fundamental American Freedoms Publications, Washington, DC (Box 96)
  - Coors Company, Adolph (Box 96)
  - Coors, Joseph [and family], 1976- (Box 97)
  - Copeland, Lamont du Pont [and family] (Box 97)
  - Copley Charities (Box 97)
  - Copley Newspapers (Box 97)
  - Copp, DeWitt S. (Box 97)
  - Copyright (Box 97)
  - Cornuelle, Richard (Box 97)
  - Corporate Data Exchange, Inc. (Box 97)
  - Coryell, James R. (Box 97)
  - Cott, Lawrence (Box 97)
  - Cotta Foundation (Box 97)
  - Cotten, Richard General, Bakersfield, CA (Box 98)
    [Broadcaster and editor-publisher See also the Group Research directory under Richard Cotten.]
  - Cotten, Richard Publications, Bakersfield, CA (Box 98)
  - Coughlin, Charles E. (Box 98)
  - Council Against Communist Aggression, 1969-70 (Box 98)
  - Council Against Communist Aggression, 1968 (Box 98)
  - Council Against Communist Aggression, 1967 (Box 98)
  - Council Against Communist Aggression, 1965-6 (Box 98)
  - Council Against Communist Aggression, 1964 (Box 98)
  - Council Against Communist Aggression, 1963 (Box 98)
  - Council Against Communist Aggression, 1961-2 (Box 98)
  - Council for a Competitive Economy (Box 99)
  - Council for a Livable World (Box 99)
  - Council for a Volunteer Military (Box 99)
  - Council for Advancement of Secondary Education (Box 99)
  - Council for Basic Education (Box 99)
  - Council for Economic Growth and Security, Inc. (Box 99)
  - Council for Freedom and Democracy (Box 99)
  - Council for Individual Freedom (Box 99)
  - Council for Inter-American Security (Box 99)
  - Council for Labor's Rank and File (Box 99)
  - Council for National Defense (Box 99)
  - Council for National Policy (Box 99)
  - Council for Private Enterprise (Box 100)
  - Council for Statehood (Box 100)
  - Council for the Defense of Freedom (Box 100)
  - Council of California Growers (Box 100)
  - Council of State Chambers of Commerce (Box 100)
  - Council of Women Citizens (Box 100)
  - Council on American Affairs (Box 100)
  - Council on American Relations (Box 100)
  - Council on Communist Anti-Semitic Policy and Practice (Box 100)
  - Council on Dangerous Drugs (Box 100)
    [See also Dangerous Drugs Foundation.]
  - Council on Economic Priorities (Box 100)
  - Council on Foreign Relations (Box 100)
  - Council on Freedom (Box 100)
  - "Councilor, The" (Box 100)
  - Counterattack (Box 100)
    [See also American Business Consultants.]
  - Counter-Insurgency Council (Box 100)
  - "Counter-Spy" (Box 100)
  - Counterthrust (Box 100)
  - Court of World Public Opinion (Box 101)
  - Courtesy Associates (Box 101)
  - Courtney, Kent and Phoebe Clippings, New Orleans, LA (Box 101)
    [See also the Group Research directory under Kent and Phoebe Courtney, "America's Unelected Rulers," "The Case of General Edwin A. Walker," "The CSA Voting Index," "The Conservative Political Action Handbook," and Special Reports -- Kent and Phoebe Courtney.]
  - Courtney, Kent and Phoebe Information on the Conservative Society of America, New Orleans, LA (Box 101)
  - Courtney, Kent and Phoebe Copies of "The Independent American", New Orleans, LA (Box 101)
  - Courtney, Kent and Phoebe Miscellaneous, New Orleans, LA (Box 101)
    [See this folder for a two-page list of cross-references.]
  - Courtney, Kent and Phoebe Pamphlets, brochures, order forms, etc., New Orleans, LA (Box 101)